A Guide to the Richard Harding Davis Papers, 1861-1915
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Letters 1879-1917, n.d. (Box 14, 15)
  - George Ade to Richard Harding Davis "Wednesday", ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
    Ade is unable to see Davis due to heavy rehearsal schedule. ANS on card of "The Wolcott" states when he can be met.
  - Sir James M. Barrie to Richard Harding Davis July 11, n.y., ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)